const quizShapes = [
    {
        question: "Q1 : A  solid object has 6 faces, 12 edges and 8 corners. This object could be a...?",
        a: "Cylinder",
        b: "Cuboid",
        c: "Cone",
        d: "Sphere",
        ans: "ans2" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q2 : How many faces does a Cube have?",
        a: "6",
        b: "8",
        c: "4",
        d: "12",
        ans: "ans1" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q3 : A perfectly round solid is called a...?",
        a: "Cylinder",
        b: "Cuboid",
        c: "Cone",
        d: "Sphere",
        ans: "ans4" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q4 : How many flat faces does a Cylinder have? ",
        a: "2",
        b: "0",
        c: "3",
        d: "6",
        ans: "ans1" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q5 : How many edges does a cube have? ",
        a: "8",
        b: "4",
        c: "6",
        d: "12",
        ans: "ans2" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q6 : What 3D shape looks like a book?",
        a: "Cylinder",
        b: "Cuboid",
        c: "Cone",
        d: "Sphere",
        ans: "ans2" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q7 : How many faces does a Sphere have?",
        a: "0",
        b: "2",
        c: "1",
        d: "4",
        ans: "ans3" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q8 : What 3D shape looks like a ball?",
        a: "Cylinder",
        b: "Cuboid",
        c: "Cone",
        d: "Sphere",
        ans: "ans4" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q9 : Which 3D shape has all equal edges?",
        a: "Cylinder",
        b: "Cube",
        c: "Cone",
        d: "Sphere",
        ans: "ans2" 
    },
    {
        question: "Q10 : How many vertices does a Cone have?",
        a: "0",
        b: "1",
        c: "2",
        d: "3",
        ans: "ans2" 
    }
];